(Howard:)Women, huh?
(Howard:)Can't live with them,
(Howard:)can't successfully
refute their hypotheses.
(Sheldon:)Amen to that.
(Penny:)Hey, Sheldon.
(Amy:)Hello.
(Penny:)I hear you broke up with Amy.
(Sheldon:)A breakup would imply
she was my girlfriend.
(Sheldon:)She was a girl who was my friend
(Sheldon:)who is now a girl who
is not my friend.
(Penny:)Wow. That's like the
worst country song ever.
(Penny:)So, how are you doing?
(Sheldon:)Regarding what?
(Sheldon:)Amy.
(Sheldon:)I don't follow.
(Penny:)Well, breakups-- or whatever the
hell this is-- can be tough.
(Sheldon:)Penny, I assure you, I'm fine.
(Sheldon:)My relationship with Amy
was purely intellectual,
(Sheldon:)There were no emotional bonds,